She lost him, but she found herself. And somehow that was everything.
Taylor Swift: The 1989 World Tour - Live is a music
film directed by Jonas Åkerlund.
Filmed in front of 76,000 fans at the ANZ Stadium in Sydney, Australia, "The 1989 World Tour Live" captures Taylor Swift's
entire performance while also mixing in behind-the-scene, rehearsal, and special guest footage from her 1989 Tour.
Self, played by Taylor Swift.
Self - Musical Guest, played by Mick Jagger.
Self - Musical Guest, played by Wiz Khalifa.
Self - Musical Guest, played by Ally Brooke.
Self - Musical Guest, played by Camila Cabello.
Self - Musical Guest, played by Dinah Jane.
Taylor Swift: The Eras Tour is a 2023 American concert film produced by the
singer-songwriter Taylor Swift and directed by Sam Wrench.
It documents the Los Angeles shows of the Eras Tour (2023–2024), Swift's sixth
headlining concert tour and the highest-grossing tour of all time.
Swift struck an unprecedented distribution agreement with AMC Theatres and Cinemark Theatres
for the film after negotiations with the major film studios fell through.
Filming took place in August 2023 across three shows at SoFi Stadium in Inglewood, California, with a
budget of $10–20 million and SAG-AFTRA permitting production to proceed amidst its 2023 strike.
Swift announced the film later that month, catching studios off guard and causing the release dates
of several films that had been set for release on or near October 13 to be moved.
The unconventional release strategy was a topic of media discourse; many journalists and industry personnel praised Swift's move to bypass the
studios to partner with theatres and opined that the move defied the traditional producer–distributor–exhibitor model of releasing films.
The film premiered at the Grove in Los Angeles on October 11, 2023,
and was released to theaters worldwide on October 13.
It was met with significant ticket demand, amassing a record $37
million on its first day of pre-sales in the U.S.
and over $100 million in total global pre-sales.
The Eras Tour became the highest-grossing concert film of all time,
earning $267.1 million in its limited theatrical run worldwide.
It received acclaim from critics, most of whom praised the direction,
spectacle, energy, and Swift's artistry and showmanship.
An extended cut of the film, subtitled (Taylor's Version), includes performances withheld from the
theatrical edit and was released on the streaming service Disney+ on March 14, 2024.
A second concert film recorded at the tour's final show on December 8, 2024, in
Vancouver, was also released on Disney+ on December 12, 2025.
Subtitled The Final Show, the film was directed by Glenn Weiss and featured The Tortured Poets
Department act that was incorporated into the tour's setlist after Wrench's film was released.
The film explores themes of concert, pop star, pop culture, pop singer, singer.